Guide to the Comic Book and Graphic Novel Collection, 1938-2012 RL.00247
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Comic Book and Graphic Novel collection
1938-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.00247
25 Linear Feet
Assortment of domestic and international comics and graphic novels acquired by the Rubenstein Library between 1980 and 2017. A large portion of the collection was originally a gift from Alicia Korenman; several other titles were removed from other Special Collections collections, including the Dorothy Allison Papers and the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection. Items in boxes 26-31 were a gift of John Canfield in 2012. Items in boxes 33-36 are a collection of a Latino comics. Over 350 titles of domestic and international comic books and graphic novels, as well as some related items, from publishers including DC/Vertigo, Abstract Studio, Oni Press, Marvel, Dark Horse, Fantagraphics, and many more.
10000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Comic Book and Graphic Novel Collection were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift and purchase in 1980-2017.
Historical Note
Assortment of domestic and international comics and graphic novels acquired by the Rubenstein Library between 1980 and 2017. A large portion of the collection was originally a gift from Alicia Korenman; several other titles were removed from other Special Collections collections, including the Dorothy Allison Papers and the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection. Also includes titles from Mexico, Denmark, France, Italy, Belgium, and Argentina. Items in boxes 26-31 were a gift of John Canfield in 2012. Items in boxes 33-36 were acquired as part of a Latino comics collection.
Collection Overview
Over 350 titles of domestic and international comics and graphic novels, as well as some related items, from publishers including DC/Vertigo, Abstract Studio, Oni Press, Marvel, Fantagraphics, and many more. There is a wide range of content present in the collection, from early super hero comics, to girl-power comics from the 1970s, to Dr. Horrible, published in 2009.
Keyword searching is the most efficient way to find a specific title in the collection, because the materials have not been arranged beyond being grouped by title. Each title is listed along with the publisher, the format, the years of publication represented in the collection, and the specific issues held in the collection. Includes notes about particular titles, such as their country of publication. Also highlighted are the small amount of titles, dated 1950s-1980s, which feature African or African American characters.
Related Material
The Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection contains over 67,000 comic books from the 1930s to 2000s. The collection is especially rich in Marvel and DC superhero comics, but contains examples of virtually every genre, publisher, and style of comic.
the Rubenstein Library also holds large collections of comics fanzines and zines by women and girls, including the Edwin and Terry Murray Fanzine Collection and the zine collections of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Teenagers -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Science fiction comic books, strips, etc.; Zines; Fantasy comic books, strips, etc.; War -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Graphic novels; Comic books, strips, etc.; African Americans -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Romance comic books, strips, etc.; Cartoonists; Animals -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Horror comic books, strips, etc.; Underground comic books, strips, etc.; Detective and mystery comic books, strips, etc.
- Comic Books and Graphic Novels, 1938-2012, 36 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Items in boxes 1-10 are gifts of Alicia Korenman, unless otherwise noted.
  Items in boxes 26-31 were a gift of John Canfield in 2012.
  Items in boxes 33-36 are a collection of Latino comics.
  - Bone: Cartoon Books, 2000-2004 (Box 1)
    Issues 38-55.
  - Cinderella: From Fabletown with Love: DC/Vertigo, 2010 (Box 1)
    Issues 1-5.
  - Fables: DC/Vertigo, 2004-2010 (Box 1)
    Issues 19-91.
  - House of Mystery: DC/Vertigo, 2008 (Box 1)
    Issues 1-3.
  - RASL: Cartoon Books, 2008-2009 (Box 1)
  - Rose: Cartoon Books, 2000-2002 (Box 1)
  - Shazam!: The Monster Society of Evil: DC, 2007 (Box 1)
    Issues 1-4.
  - Stupid, Stupid Rat-Tails: Cartoon Books, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Echo: Abstract Studio, 2008-2009 (Box 2)
    Issues 1-10, 14, 16-18.
  - Paradise Too!: Abstract Studio, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
  - Strangers in Paradise: Antarctic Press; Homage Comics; Image; Abstract Studio, 1993, 1996-2007 (Box 2)
    One-shot.
  - Strangers in Paradise magnet set (Box 2)
  - Strangers in Paradise Source Book: Abstract Studio, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Strangers in Paradise: I Dream of You: Abstract Studio, 1996 (Box 2)
    Graphic novel.
  - Strangers in Paradise: Immortal Enemies: Abstract Studio, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Strangers in Paradise: It's a Good Life!: Abstract Studio, 1996 (Box 2)
  - The Collected Strangers in Paradise, Vol. 1: Abstract Studio, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Amy Racecar Color Special: El Capitan, 1997, 1999 (Box 3)
    Issues 1-2.
  - Artbabe: Fantagraphics, 1996-1999 (Box 3)
    Vol. 1 no. 5, Vol. 2 no. 1-4.
  - Biff Bam Pow!: Amaze Ink/Slave Labor Graphics, 2007 (Box 3)
    Issue 1.
  - Blue Monday: Painted Moon: Oni Press, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
  - Blue Monday: The Kids Are Alright: Oni Press, 2000 (Box 3)
    Issue 2.
  - Blue Monday: Thieves Like Us: Oni Press, 2008 (Box 3)
  - Breakfast After Noon: Oni Press, 2000-2001 (Box 3)
    Issues 1-6.
  - CharmSchool: Slave Labor Graphics, 2000-2003 (Box 3)
    Issues 1-9.
  - Dork: Slave Labor Graphics, 2000-2006 (Box 3)
    Issues 8-11.
  - Hopeless Savages: Oni Press, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Hopeless Savages: B-Sides: The Origin of the Dusted Bunnies: Oni Press, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Hopeless Savages: Ground Zero: Oni Press, 2002 (Box 3)
  - La Perdida: Fantagraphics, 2001-2005 (Box 3)
  - Little Star: Oni Press, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Love Fights: Oni Press, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
    Issues 1-12.
  - Optic Nerve: Drawn & Quarterly, 1995-2007 (Box 3)
    Issues 1-11.
  - Pop Gun War: Cryptic Press, 2000-2002 (Box 3)
  - Radio: An Illustrated Guide: WBEZ, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Scary Godmother: Sirius, 2001-2002 (Box 3)
    Issues 1-3, 5-6.
  - Scooter Girl: Oni Press, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
    Issues 1, 3-6.
  - Scott Pilgrim: Oni Press, 2006 (Box 3)
    2006 Free Comic Book Day one-shot giveaway.
  - Slow News Day: Slave Labor Graphics, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Strangetown: Oni Press, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Stray Bullets: El Capitan, 1995, 2003 (Box 3)
    Issues 7, 31-32.
  - Sugar Buzz: Slave Labor Graphics, 1998 (Box 3)
    Issues 1, 3-5.
  - THB: Comics from Mars: AdHouse Books, 2007 (Box 3)
  - Too Much Hopeless Savages: Oni Press, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
  - Where's It At, Sugar Rat?: Slave Labor Graphics, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Young Liars: DC/Vertigo, 2008 (Box 3)
  - American Splendor: DC/Vertigo, 2006, 2008 (Box 4)
    Issues 1, Vol. 2 no. 1.
  - American Virgin: DC/Vertigo, 2006 (Box 4)
    Issues 5-6.
  - Army @ Love: DC/Vertigo, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Bang! Tango: DC/Vertigo, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Bipolar: Alternative Comics, 2004 (Box 4)
    Issue 5.
  - Bite Club: Vampire Crime Unit: DC/Vertigo, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Black Summer: Avatar, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Caper: DC, 2003-2004 (Box 4)
  - Comics Festival!: Toronto Comic Arts Festival, 2005 (Box 4)
    2005 Free Comic Book Day one-shot giveaway.
  - Crossing Midnight: DC/Vertigo, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Deadman: DC/Vertigo, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Evil Eye: Fantagraphics, 2004 (Box 4)
    Issue 11.
  - Faker: DC/Vertigo, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Fillerbunny: Slave Labor Graphics, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Greatest Hits: DC/Vertigo, 2008 (Box 4)
  - I Feel Sick: Slave Labor Graphics, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Johnny the Homicidal Maniac: Slave Labor Graphics, 1995 (Box 4)
  - JTHM: Director's Cut: Slave Labor Graphics, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Kabuki: Image, 1998-1999, 2001 (Box 4)
    Issues 3-6, 8, 1/2.
  - Kabuki Agents: Scarab: Image, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Kabuki Classics: Image, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Kabuki: Images: Image, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - Kabuki: Reflections: Marvel/Icon, 2006 (Box 4)
    Issues 6-7.
  - Kabuki: The Alchemy: Marvel/Icon, 2004-2007 (Box 4)
  - Kabuki: The Ghost Play: Image, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Northlanders: DC/Vertigo, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Owly: Breakin' the Ice: Top Shelf Productions, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Plastic Man: DC, 2005, 2006 (Box 4)
    Issues 18, 20.
  - Road Trip: Oni Press, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Sky Between Branches: Com.x, 2002 (Box 4)
    Issue 0.
  - Squee!: Slave Labor Graphics, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
  - Strangehaven: Abiogenesis Press, 1997-2005 (Box 4)
    Issues 7-18.
  - Strangehaven: Arcadia: Abiogenesis Press, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Sweet: Adept Books, 1999 (Box 4)
    Issues 3-5.
  - The Adventures of Barry Ween, Boy Genius: Oni Press, 1999 (Box 4)
  - The Adventures of Barry Ween, Boy Genius: Monkey Tales: Oni Press, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - The Other Side: DC/Vertigo, 2006 (Box 4)
  - The Un-Men: DC/Vertigo, 2007 (Box 4)
  - The Vinyl Underground: DC/Vertigo, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Unknown Soldier: DC/Vertigo, 2008 (Box 4)
  - 1602: Marvel, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
    Issues 1-8.
  - Air: DC/Vertigo, 2008-2009 (Box 5)
  - Astonishing X-Men: Marvel, 2006-2008 (Box 5)
    Issues 13-25, Giant-Size no. 1.
  - Astonishing X-Men: Dangerous: Marvel, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Astonishing X-Men: Gifted: Marvel, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Black Orchid: DC/Vertigo, 1991 (Box 5)
  - DC: The New Frontier: DC, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Eternals: Marvel, 2006-2007 (Box 5)
    Issues 1-7.
  - Gods & Tulips: Westhampton House, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Madame Xanadu: DC/Vertigo, 2008-2010 (Box 5)
    Issues 1-18.
  - My Faith in Frankie: DC/Vertigo, 2004 (Box 5)
  - NYX: No Way Home: Marvel, 2008-2009 (Box 5)
  - Sandman Mystery Theatre: Sleep of Reason: DC/Vertigo, 2007 (Box 5)
  - The Books of Magic: DC/Vertigo, 1993 (Box 5)
  - The Books of Magic: Bindings: DC/Vertigo, 1995 (Box 5)
  - The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen: America's Best Comics, 1999-2000 (Box 5)
    Issues 2-6.
  - The Sandman Presents: Deadboy Detectives: DC/Vertigo, 2001 (Box 5)
  - The Sandman Presents: Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Dreams… But Were Afraid to Ask: DC/Vertigo, 2001 (Box 5)
  - The Umbrella Academy: Apocalypse Suite: Dark Horse, 2007-2008 (Box 5)
  - The Umbrella Academy: Dallas: Dark Horse, 2008-2009 (Box 5)
  - The Unwritten: DC/Vertigo, 2008-2010 (Box 5)
    Issues 1-2, 4-8.
  - Vertigo: Winter's Edge: DC/Vertigo, 1998-2000 (Box 5)
  - Blondin et Cirage: Le Negre Blanc: Dupuis, 1984 (Box 6)
    Graphic novel (reprint).
  - Dead Herring Comics: Actus Independent Comics, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Delphine: Fantagraphics and Coconino Press, 2006 (Box 6)
  - Epoxy: Epoxy Press, 2002 (Box 6)
    Issue 3.
  - Fancy Froglin's Sexy Forest: Alternative Comics, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Girlhero: High Drive Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
  - Interiorae: Fantagraphics and Coconino Press, 2006 (Box 6)
  - Jojo et Jimmy: La Tremblote: Societe d'Editions Periodiques, 1960 (Box 6)
    One-shot. Published in Belgium. Features African or African-American characters.
  - Love and Rockets: Fantagraphics, 1987, 1989, 1993-1995 (Box 6)
    Issues 23, 30, 42-44, 48.
  - Love and Rockets Bonanza!: Fantagraphics, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Mouse Guard: Archaia Studios Press, 2006 (Box 6)
  - Paranoid: Tales of Neurosis: Joe Deagnon, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Super F*ckers: Top Shelf Productions, 2005-2007 (Box 6)
    Issues 271, 273, 277, 279.
  - Sweet Gwendoline and the Missing Princess: Centurian Publications, 1982 (Box 6)
    One-shot. From the Dorothy Allison Papers.
  - Sweeter Gwen and the Return of Gwendoline: Belier Press, 1976 (Box 6)
  - The Adventures of Baby Dyke: Terry Sapp, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 6)
  - The Hookah Girl and Other True Stories: Growing Up Christian Palestinian in America: Marguerite Dabaie, 2007 (Box 6)
    Vol. 1.
  - The Sketchbook Diaries: Top Shelf Productions, 2001-2004 (Box 6)
  - Twisted Sisters: Kitchen Sink Comix, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Your Flesh Quarterly: Fantagraphics, 1997 (Box 6)
    Issue 34.
  - Jeunes Annees: Konan et Amena: Francs et Franches Camarades, 1967 (Box 6)
    Vol. 15 no. 9.
  - Keni: Artima, 1957 (Box 6)
    Issues 13, 19.
  - Achilles Storm: Aja Blu Comix, 1991 (Box 7)
    Issue 7. From the Dorothy Allison Papers.
  - Action Girl Comics: Slave Labor Graphics, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Bamboula: Fait des Farces: Editions Rouff, 1953 (Box 7)
    One-shot. Published in France. Features African or African-American characters.
  - Beatrix Dominatrix, 1995 (Box 7)
    Scope and Contents
  - Bibi Fricotin: Societe Parisienne d'Edition, 1981 (Box 7)
    Issue 43. Published in France. Features African or African American characters.
  - Bloody Wymmin Comix: Bloody Wymmin Comix, 1994 (Box 7)
    Issue 1. From the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Come Out Comix: Portland Women's Resource Center, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Cuckoo: Green Door Studios, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
    Issues 2, 4. From the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Dirty Plotte: Drawn & Quarterly, 1991-1995 (Box 7)
  - Diva: Starhead Comix, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Fanny: Knockabout; Carol Bennett, 1991-1993 (Box 7)
  - Friends of Lulu Presents: Broad Appeal: Friends of Lulu, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Gay Comix/Gay Comics: Kitchen Sink Comix; Bob Ross, 1981, 1986, 1991, 1993 (Box 7)
    Issues 2, 8, 13, 19. Issue 19 from the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Girl Fight Comics: Print Mint, 1972, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Girltalk: Fantagraphics, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
    Issues 1-3. Issue 1 from the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection; Issues 2-3 from the Paula Kamen Papers.
  - Good Girls: Fantagraphics, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    Issues 1-4. From the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Hopster's Tracks: Bongo, 2000 (Box 7)
    Issue 2. From the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection
  - Hothead Paisan: Homicidal Lesbian Terrorist: Giant Ass Publishing, 1991-1995 (Box 7)
    Issues 2, 6-7, 12-13, 15-17, 19-20.
  - Le Journal de Bebe: Albin Michel, 1938 (Box 7)
    Issue 348.
  - Mandrake: Edizioni Fratelli Spada, 1964 (Box 7)
    Issue 78.
  - Naughty Bits: Fantagraphics, 1992 (Box 7)
    Issue 7.
  - New Funnies: Dell, 1942 (Box 7)
    Issue 69.
  - Oh… Her Comic Quarterly: B Publications, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    Issues 9-11. From the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Out In Comics: Out In Comics Group, 2002 (Box 7)
    Issue 4.
  - Pandoras Box Comix: Nanny Goat Productions, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Princess Maetrex: Dollhouse Comics, 1998 (Box 7)
    Issue 1, two variant covers. From the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Prism Comics: Your LGBT Guide to Comics: Prism Comics, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Reactor Girl: Tragedy Strikes Press, 1991-1993 (Box 7)
  - Real Girl: Fantagraphics, 1991-1994 (Box 7)
    Issues 2-7. Issue 7 bound with Girltalk no. 1
  - Slutburger: Drawn & Quarterly, 1991-1993, 1995 (Box 7)
    Issues 1-5. Issue 5 from the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Tales of the Closet, 1987-1990 (Box 7)
  - The Sisterhood of Steel: Marvel/Epic, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
    Issues 1, 3-7. From the Dorothy Allison Papers.
  - Tits & Clits Comix: Last Gasp, 1979-1980, 1987 (Box 7)
    Issues 1, 3, 5-6.
  - Very Vicky: Meet Danny Ocean, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Way Out Strips: Tragedy Strikes Press; Fantagraphics, 1992, 1994 (Box 7)
    Vol. 2, no. 1-3, and Vol. 3, no. 1-3. Vol. 3 no. 1 from the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection.
  - Welcome to the Dollhouse: Dollhouse Comics, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Wendy Whitebread: Eros Comix, 1990 (Box 7)
    Issue 1. From the Dorothy Allison Papers.
  - Wimmen's Comix: Last Gasp; Rip Off Press, 1973-1976, 1983-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
    Issues 2-11, 13-14, 16-17.
  - Dynamite Damsels: Roberta Gregory, 1976 (Box 7)
    One-shot. From the Ladyslipper Music Records.
  - Castle Waiting: Cartoon Books; Olio; Fantagraphics, 2000-2003; 2006-2009 (Box 8)
    Issues 1-4, 12-16; Vol. 2, no. 1-15.
  - Finder: Light Speed Press, 2002-2005 (Box 8)
    1998 one-shot giveaway; 25-38.
  - Girl Crazy: Dark Horse, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Love and Rockets: Fantagraphics, 2001-2007 (Box 8)
    Vol 2, issues 1-20.
  - Luba: Fantagraphics, 1998-2004 (Box 8)
    Issues 1-3, 5-10.
  - Luba's Comics and Stories: Fantagraphics, 2000-2006 (Box 8)
  - Maggie and Hopey Color Special: Fantagraphics, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Measles: Fantagraphics, 1998-2001 (Box 8)
    Issues 1-4, 6-8.
  - New Love: Fantagraphics, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
  - Penny Century: Fantagraphics, 1997-2000 (Box 8)
  - Speak of the Devil: Dark Horse, 2007-2008 (Box 8)
  - Tales from Shock City: Fantagraphics, 2001 (Box 8)
  - Ten Years of Love and Rockets: Fantagraphics, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Whoa, Nellie!: Fantagraphics, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Yeah!: DC, 1999-2000 (Box 8)
    Issues 1-6, 9.
  - Atlas: Drawn & Quarterly, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Batman: A Death in the Family: DC, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Batman: Harley Quinn: DC, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Belly Button Comix: Oog & Blik/Fantagraphics, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Berlin: Drawn & Quarterly, 2002-2008 (Box 9)
    Issues 9-16.
  - Cheat: Oni Press, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Drinks and Dancing: Boy Who Cried, 2002 (Box 9)
    Zine.
  - Ex Machina: Special Edition: Wildstorm/DC, 2005 (Box 9)
    One-shot giveaway.
  - Ex Machina: Tag: Wildstorm/DC, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Ex Machina: The First Hundred Days: Wildstorm/DC, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Family Reunion: Small Beer Press, 2004 (Box 9)
    One-shot giveaway: "A comic from the novel Perfect Circle."
  - Forlorn Funnies: Absence of Ink, 2002-2003 (Box 9)
    Issues 2-4.
  - From the Curve: Robert K. Ullman, 1998 (Box 9)
    Zine, no. 4.
  - Grand Gestures: Alternative Comics, 2003 (Box 9)
  - How to Understand Israel in Sixty Days or Less: Sarah Glidden, 2007-2008 (Box 9)
  - Jetlag: Actus Tragicus, 1998 (Box 9)
    Issue 14: "Stories by Etgar Keret."
  - Jin & Jam: Sparkplug Comic Books, 2008 (Box 9)
  - Korgi: Top Shelf Productions, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Kyle Baker Cartoonist: Kyle Baker, 2005 (Box 9)
    Vol. 2.
  - Love as a Foreign Language: Oni Press, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Lucky: Drawn & Quarterly, 2007 (Box 9)
    Vol 2 no. 1.
  - Lunch Hour Comix: Alternative Comics, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Mildred Lee: Space Station Schoolgirl: John Pham, ca. 2004 (Box 9)
  - Or Else: Drawn & Quarterly, 2004-2005, 2008 (Box 9)
    Issues 1-3, 5.
  - Peanut Butter and Jeremy: Alternative Comics, 2000-2001 (Box 9)
    Isues 1-2.
  - Postcard booklet advertising Minx graphic novels, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Shirley: A Sex Comedy: Dimona Comix Group, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Slave Labor Peepshow: Slave Labor Graphics, 2000 (Box 9)
    Vol. 2, no. 6-7.
  - Tales Designed to Thrizzle: Fantagraphics, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
  - The Horrible Truth About Comics: Alternative Comics, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Why I Like Bugs: Dan Moynihan, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Works & Days: Preview Book: Boy Who Cried, n.d. (Box 9)
  - World Enough and Time: Part I of Works & Days: Boy Who Cried, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Y: The Last Man: DC/Vertigo, 2002-2008 (Box 9)
    Issues 1-60.
  - Yikes!: Alternative Press, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    Vol 2, no. 1-2.
  - Angel: After the Fall: IDW, 2007 (Box 10)
  - Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Season Eight: Dark Horse, 2007-2009 (Box 10)
    Issues 1-30.
  - Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Tales of the Vampires: Dark Horse, 2009 (Box 10)
  - Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Willow: Dark Horse, 2009 (Box 10)
  - Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Willow and Tara: Dark Horse, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Buffy the Vampire Slayer: Willow and Tara: Wilderness: Dark Horse, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Dr. Horrible: Dark Horse, 2009 (Box 10)
  - Marvel Romance Redux: But I Thought He Loved Me!: Marvel, 2006 (Box 10)
  - Marvel Romance Redux: Love Is a Four-Letter Word: Marvel, 2006 (Box 10)
  - Marvel Romance Redux: Restraining Orders are for Other Girls: Marvel, 2006 (Box 10)
  - Powers: Image; Marvel/Icon, 2002-2008, 2010 (Box 10)
    Vol. 1, no. 21-23, 25-37; Vol. 2, no. 1-30; Annual, no. 1; Vol. 3, no. 2.
  - Preacher: DC/Vertigo, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
    Issues 51-59, 62-66.
  - Preacher Special: One Man's War: DC/Vertigo, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Preacher Special: Tall in the Saddle: DC/Vertigo, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Supermarket: IDW, 2006 (Box 10)
  - Leyendas de América: Editorial Novaro, 1959-1961 (Box 10)
    Issues 38, 40, 45-47, 49, 51-66. Published in Mexico.
  - Leyendas de América: Editorial Novaro, 1961-1973 (Box 11)
    Issues 67-112, 114, 116-119, 121-124, 127, 129-132, 134-136, 138-146, 148-149, 151, 153, 155-161, 163, 165, 168-172, 180-182, 186, 191-196, 198-202, 204-206. Published in Mexico.
  - Illustrerede Klassikere: Stig Jensen, n.d. (Box 11)
    Issue 17: Moby Dick. Published in Denmark. From the Gay Wilson Allen Papers.
  - El Payo: Un Hombre Contra el Mundo!: Editoria Senda, 1966-1971 (Box 12)
    Issues 1-3, 5, 9, 10, 14, 20, 23, 25, 31-36, 38, 39, 41-50, 52, 54-65, 67-88, 90, 102, 104, 106, 108, 110, 112-129, 131, 132-147, 149-150, 152-187, 189-197, 199. Published in Mexico.
  - Tit-Bits: Ediciones Record, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
    Issues 1-10. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Tit-Bits Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1976 (Box 13)
    Issue 1. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Tit-Bits: Ediciones Record, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
    Issues 11-20. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Tit-Bits Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1977 (Box 14)
    Issue 2. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Tit-Bits: Ediciones Record, 1977-78 (Box 15)
    Issues 21-30. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Tit-Bits Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1978 (Box 15)
    Issue 3. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Tit-Bits: Ediciones Record, 1978 (Box 16)
    Issues 31-40, anuario no. 1. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Corto Maltes: Ediciones Record, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
  - Skorpio Suplemento Extra: Ediciones Record, 1974 (Box 17)
    Issue 1. Published in Argentina; bound with no. 10 of "Corto Maltes."
  - Corto Maltes: Ediciones Record, 1975-1977 (Box 18)
    Issues 11-20, anuario no. 1. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Corto Maltes Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Corto Maltes: Ediciones Record, 1977 (Box 19)
    Issies 21-30. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Corto Maltes Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Corto Maltes: Ediciones Record, 1978 (Box 20)
    Issues 31-40. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed with some loss.
  - Pif-Paf: Ediciones Record, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
    Issues 1-10. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed.
  - Pif-Paf: Ediciones Record, 1976-1977 (Box 22)
    Issues 11-20. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed.
  - Pif-Paf Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1976 (Box 22)
    Issue 1. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed.
  - Pif-Paf: Ediciones Record, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
    Issues 21-30. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed.
  - Pif-Paf Libro de Oro: Ediciones Record, 1977 (Box 23)
    Issue 2. Published in Argentina; bound and trimmed.
  - Tit-Bits: Ediciones Record, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
    Issues 41-45, 47-52, 57-58, 60, anuario no. 2. Published in Argentina.
  - Gunga Din: Ediciones Record, n.d. (Box 24)
    Issue 1. Published in Argentina; printed in Brasil.
  - Hora Cero: Ediciones de la Urraca, 1990 (Box 24)
    Issues 1-2. Published in Argentina.
  - Mad Follies: E.C., 1965 (Box 24)
  - Mad Special: E.C., 1971, 1973, 1975, 1976 (Box 24)
    Issues 5, 10, 17, 20. Gift of James Albert; later titled "Mad Super-Special."
  - More Trash from Mad: E.C., 1958-1960 (Box 24)
  - The Worst from Mad: E.C., 1960 (Box 24)